
// Array of objects
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: '	How long ______ English?',
        options: ['do you learn','are you learning','have you been learning','you learn'],
        answer: 'have you been learning'
      },
    
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Can you tell me when ______ ?",
        
        options:['the train leaves','does the train leave','leaves the train','does leave the train'],
        answer: 'the train leaves'
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:'Did you speak to Juliet?" "No, I have ______ seen her.',
        options:['nearly','hardly','often','always'],
        answer: 'hardly'
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:'I want to be a teacher when I ______.',
        options:['grow','aged','grow up','am more years'],
        answer: 'grow up'
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:'I donot like coffee.______ do I.',
        options:['So','Neither','Either','No'],
        answer: 'Neither'
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:'By this time next year, I ______ all my exams',
        options:['will have taken','will take','take','have taken'],
        answer: 'will have taken'
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:'I went to the shop ______ some chocolate.',
        options:['for buying','for buy','to buy','buy'],
        answer: 'to buy'
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:'They have put speed bumps on the road to ______ accidents',
        options:['avoid','prohibit','prevent','forbid'],
        answer: 'prevent'
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:'Where is the ______ post office, please?',
        options:['most near','near','more near','nearest'],
        answer: 'nearest'
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:'You should ______ swimming',
        options:['start up','get off','take up','take off'],
        answer: 'take up'
    },
]